因此，下一部分是层。
So the next section is layers.
我们要谈一下建筑的性能。
And we're gonna talk a little
bit about build performance.
这不是你需要担心的事情
Which is not something you have to
worry an enormous amount about.
但我要告诉你当你开发这个应用的时候
But I will tell you that while
you're developing this app,
每次您更改文件时。
every time that you a change a file.
这是项目内部的文件已更改，是吗 ?
This is a file inside of
the project is changed, right?
所以说我决定了，这个应该是五千，而不是 3000，对吧 ?
So let's say I decided, this should
run on 5000 instead of 3000, right?
我要去改变这个
And I go in and change that.
现在，如果我再次运行 Docker 构建，那么它将转至类似的点，
Now if I run Docker build again,
it is going to go to the points like okay,
这个没有改变，这个没有改变，这个没有改变，
this didn't change, this didn't change,
this didn't change,
这个没有改变，这个没有改变，这个没有改变。
this didn't change, this didn't change,
this didn't change.
在这里这条线 COPY 这条线
Right, here, this line, COPY, this line.
因为档案系统是不同的
Because the file system is
different it takes a quick hash of
就像以前的样子
what it looked like before.
就好像他们改变了什么
It's like, they changed something.
从这里开始就开始了对吧
So it's gonna start from this
instruction right here, right?
所以这些只使用以前所有的缓存层，对吧 ?
So these ones that just uses all
the cached layers from before, right?
我给你看了这些数字
I showed you those numbers.
就从这里开始但这事有多烦人
It just starts here, but
what's annoying about this is,
它会把它复制过来然后那之后它会立即运行什么呢
is that it'll copy this over and then
what does it run immediately after that?
npm 安装占用了很多时间，使用了带宽，并且是浪费的权利吗 ?
npm install which takes a lot of time,
uses bandwidth, and it's wasteful right?
如果我们能在晚上进行 npm 的安装，然后再进行复制，岂不是很棒吗 ?
Wouldn't it be nice if we could just
run npm install and then do the copy?
这就是一层层的想法。
That's kind of the idea here with layers.
就好像你是按秩序来考虑的对吧
As if you think about things
in the proper order, right?
然后，您可以利用此高速缓存来利用以下事实 :
Then you can leverage this caching to be
able to take advantage of the fact that
这将进行高速缓存。
this is cached.
所以我现在就去做同样的项目
So, I'm just gonna do this on
the same projects right now.
有一层，这也比较是一样的。
There's a layers,
this is relatively the same thing.
所以我要留在这里更复杂的节点项目
So I am just gonna stay here in
the more complicated node project.
所以在 WORKDIR 中他们会来这里
So here in WORKDIR,
they are going to come in here and
我们要先在这儿复印一份
we are gonna do a copy here first.
所以我们要复印两份
So we're gonna do two copies.
我要说副本， --chown node:node。
I'm gonna say copy, --chown node:node.
我要把 package-lock.json 和
And I'm gonna copy
the package-lock.json and
Package.json 到这里对吧
the package.json to here, right?
你得把这个斜杠放在那个目录里，对吧 ?
You have to put the slash that to know
to put it in the directory, right?
好吧那我就去参加晚上的工作
Okay then I'm gonna run npm ci.
我要在这之后再做任何事
RUN npm ci, and
then I'm gonna do everything after that.
我只是想说副本节点 : 节点，时间段，时间段，对吗 ?
I'm just gonna say copy node:node,
period, period, right?
我要摆脱这一切
And I'm gonna get rid of this.
现在，这个问题变得更加复杂了。
Now, this made this a little
bit more complicated.
但现在我改变我的档案
But now any time I change one of my files,
它会保留 npm 的高速缓存层对吧
it's gonna keep that cached
layer of npm installs, right?
所以我要开车回家
So just to drive home my point,
我要做船坞的建造或者建码头对吧
I'm gonna do docker run build,
or docker build, right?
所以它会先运行一次，对吧 ?
So it's gonna run the ci one first, right?
我只是改变了所有这些东西的顺序。
Cuz it hasn't done that yet cuz I just
changed the order of all that stuff.
现在让我们做个改变，我把这个改成了 5000。
Now let's go ahead and change this,
I changed this to 5000.
我们把它改回 3000吧
Let's change it back to 3000.
先前，它将再次完成 npm 安装。
Previously, it would have
done the npm install again.
但如果我这么做再做一次
But now if I just do this and do it again,
通知就在最后就被复制了对吧
notice it just skips right to
the copy at the end, right?
重建速度非常快。
And that rebuilt really fast.
>> 这是因为软件包锁或包 json 没有更改吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Is that because package lock or
package json did not change?
>> Right，在 package.json 或包锁定中未更改任何内容。
&gt;&gt; Right, I didn't change anything
in package.json or package lock.
一旦我改变了某件事就会再次出现
As soon as I change something in there,
then it'll run that step again.
> > 所以它已经知道它是有条件的
&gt;&gt; So it already knows it's
kinda conditional on that.
> > 是。 >> 进来。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Come in.
>> Right，假定没有变化，那么这是 -
&gt;&gt; Right, it assumes if nothing changed,
then this is-
>> 现在使用高速缓存。
&gt;&gt; Now with the cache.
>> Right，它关于高速缓存，您将获得高速缓存命中。
&gt;&gt; Right, it's about cache,
you'll get a cache hit.
有道理
That makes sense.?
>> 所以顺序非常重要。
&gt;&gt; So the order is really important.
> > 非常，对，对，就像洋葱一样，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Very, yep, cuz it's,
it's like an onion, right?
它是在层层之上的层之上的层之上的建筑层。
It's building layers on top of layers
on top of layers on top of layers.
Docker 容器是这样工作的。
That's how Docker containers work.
想想就很聪明，对吧 ?
It's really clever when
you think about it, right?
它是可重复的
Cuz it's repeatable.
所以这事最让人担心的对吧
So the one concern with this, right?
特别是，如果您的 CI 系统正在维护 Docker 高速缓存。
In particular, if your CI system
is maintaining a Docker cache.
事实上，其中许多人并不是出于这个原因。
Many of them don't,
actually, for this reason.
如果有安全的补丁就会发生的对吧
Is that, what happens if there's
a security patch, right?
所以说我在这里看我的 package.json。
So let's say I'm looking
here at my package.json.
我哈皮 18.4
I have hapi 18.4.
比如说 18.4.1 是吧 ?
Let's say 18.4.1 comes out, right?
如果我现在做个晚上的安装我会明白的对吧
If I do an npm install right now,
I would get that, right?
因为这里是一个相对的版本，这就是这个照护者的意思。
Because this is a relative version here,
that's what the caret means.
但我要把那个缓存的 Docker 层
But I'll have that cached Docker
layer that it won't pick up that,
cuz 它不是在运行 npm-重新安装，对吧 ?
cuz it's not running npm-install again,
right?
因此，在此意义上，您可以从该特定透视图中获取旧高速缓存。
So in that sense, you can get a stale
cache from that particular perspective.
它通常只影响到您的开发。
It usually only affects
you in development.
我不太在意我是否得到安全贴补
And I don't really care if I
get a security patch when I'm
在本地运行。
running it locally.
可能是一千九百次
999 times out of 1,000 probably.
但你应该知道这事也许会发生在你身上
But it's just something you should
know that might be happening to you.